101webdesigns.com 2014-06-07

# Privacy Policy And Use of Cookies -

**Privacy Policy**

101webdesigns.com is composed by a team of writers that take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy policy document, we outline the type of personal data received and collected by 101webdesigns and how they are used.

**Log Files**

101webdesigns uses log files like many other online sites. The log files contain information that include your IP address and ISP, the type of browser you are using, date and time stamp as well as exit and referring pages. The amount of clicks you made is also recorded in the log files to help in managing the website, getting demographic information, analyzing trends and tracking the whereabouts inside the website. Such data is not associated with anything that can is personally identifiable.

**Email Newsletter**

If you sign up to our weekly newsletter we will keep you email address save. Your privacy is important to us, therefore we will never share your email address with third party advertisers. You can choose to unsubscribe whenever you want. Just click the “unsubscribe” link in one of the newsletters we send to you.

**Web Beacons and Cookies**

101webdesigns uses cookies in order to record user specific information on accessed or visited pages and save your preferences. Cookies are also utilized to customize content according to your browser and other information sent through it.

**Double Click DART Cookie**

Google is a third party vendor that uses cookies to serve ads on 10webdesigns.com. Google’s use of DART cookies allows it to place advertisements according to your visits on our website and other sites. You may opt out of the DART cookie at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. It is the privacy policy on Google ads and content. Our advertisement partners may also utilize cookies and web beacons within 101webdesigns.com.

Ads and links technology is used by third party ad servers and networks to send ads appearing on our website to your browser directly. The process automatically records your IP address. Other technologies such as web beacons, JavaScript and cookies may also be used by third party advertisers to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or personalize ad content.

101webdesigns.com does not have access or control over cookies utilized by third party ads. You may choose not to use some of these cookies by going to [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

If you require more information or want to ask questions about our privacy policy, please contact us through email at: [contact@101webdesigns.com](mailto:%20contact@101webdesigns.com) **  
**
